Hi!
Okay now we are going to work with our garlic and once again a good way to peel garlic is to twist it and get a little pop there and then the skin would peel right off.
Let's see and lets try something else I smash my garlic a lot of time before I chop it anyways but I have always been told if you take with the skin on and just hit it that is another way to get the skin off really easy.
I didn't seem that easy I like my method better but there it comes.
Take that part off.
Anyway like I said I smash my garlic, give a little smash or if you have some gadgets you can just put it in a small chopper and chop your garlic up.
Of course you can do your onions like that, you can do your bell pepper, I wouldn't suggest tomato unless you want your tomato puree more then chopped.
But we would chop our garlic up give a nice and edible and in spaghetti many times or in any dish a lot of times it is not a pleasant thing to just come across a big chunk of garlic as your eating unless your like me and you like garlic you look forward to that.
Anyway we can chop our garlic, garlic I love it.
A friend and I where traveling together and came across a place that serves this garlic cloves amazing we have been looking forward every since but we where over seas.
Anyway here is our garlic and we would add that to our onions and set it aside as we continue to build our ingredients and our base for our sauce.